[
	{
		"question": "但愿人长久",
		"answer": "祝寿",
		"options": [
			"两相好",
			"田家乐",
			"守岁"
		],
		"explain": "祝寿"
	},
	{
		"question": "奖励玉盘一个",
		"answer": "赏月",
		"options": [
			"元宵灯会",
			"阔时节",
			"抓周"
		],
		"explain": "赏月"
	},
	{
		"question": "你潇洒，我漂亮",
		"answer": "两相好",
		"options": [
			"送人情",
			"过生日",
			"花儿会"
		],
		"explain": "两相好"
	},
	{
		"question": "人行春色里 ",
		"answer": "踏青",
		"options": [
			"花灯",
			"秋生",
			"花儿会"
		],
		"explain": "踏青"
	},
	{
		"question": "上官封后，一夜出头",
		"answer": "守岁",
		"options": [
			"花灯",
			"抓周",
			"办满月"
		],
		"explain": "守岁"
	},
	{
		"question": "万紫千红开满园",
		"answer": "花儿会",
		"options": [
			"送人情",
			"秋生",
			"踏青"
		],
		"explain": "花儿会"
	},
	{
		"question": "喜看稻菽千重浪",
		"answer": "田家乐",
		"options": [
			"两相好",
			"祝寿",
			"守岁"
		],
		"explain": "田家乐"
	},
	{
		"question": "一夜鱼龙舞",
		"answer": "元宵灯会",
		"options": [
			"赏月",
			"阔时节",
			"抓周"
		],
		"explain": "元宵灯会"
	},
	{
		"question": "金猴奋起千钧棒",
		"answer": "扫尘",
		"options": [
			"祭灶",
			"赏月",
			"守岁"
		],
		"explain": "扫尘"
	},
	{
		"question": "连续操劳三十天",
		"answer": "办满月",
		"options": [
			"抓周",
			"守岁",
			"两相好"
		],
		"explain": "办满月"
	}
]